let questions = [{"numb": 1, "question": "violence, Himse, dourjanya", "answer": "Gewalt", "options": ["Gewalt", "Froh", "Erfolg", "Perspektiv"]}, {"numb": 2, "question": "department, vibhaga", "answer": "Fachbereich", "options": ["Vertrieb", "\u00fcbersicht", "Kohlenstoff", "Fachbereich"]}, {"numb": 3, "question": "available, kannada : Labhyavide, Doraku", "answer": "Verf\u00fcgbar", "options": ["Friedlich", "Randale", "Verf\u00fcgbar", "Beglaubigte"]}, {"numb": 4, "question": "opinion, view, abhipraya, nota", "answer": "Ansicht", "options": ["Ansicht", "ben\u00f6tigt", "widerlich", "ewig"]}, {"numb": 5, "question": "torture, chitrahimse", "answer": "Qual", "options": ["aktiv", "Ernst", "Qual", "laut + dativ, laut + gen"]}, {"numb": 6, "question": "non violence, ahimse", "answer": "Gewaltlosigkeit", "options": ["Kommunikation", "Gewaltlosigkeit", "befristet", "Fehlerlos"]}, {"numb": 7, "question": "defeat, solu", "answer": "Niederlage", "options": ["besondere", "Niederlage", "bestimmt", "Ansprechpartner"]}, {"numb": 8, "question": "temporary, taatkalika", "answer": "befristet", "options": ["Betrug", "befristet", "politisch", "ben\u00f6tigt"]}, {"numb": 9, "question": "waste, garbage", "answer": "Abfall", "options": ["widernat\u00fcrlich", "Abfall", "widerlich", "W\u00fcrde"]}, {"numb": 10, "question": "Oxygen", "answer": "Sauerstoff", "options": ["Sauerstoff", "Chaos", "Kohlenstoff", "bestimmt"]}, {"numb": 11, "question": "resource, sampanmoola", "answer": "Ressource", "options": ["Infrastruktur", "Abfall", "Ressource", "Fr\u00f6hlich"]}, {"numb": 12, "question": "area, Kshetra", "answer": "Bereich", "options": ["Nutzung", "Bereich", "Kommunikation", "inzwischen"]}, {"numb": 13, "question": "Covert (Religion)", "answer": "Konvertierung", "options": ["Beglaubigte", "Konvertierung", "bestimmt", "Fehlerlos"]}, {"numb": 14, "question": "approach, strategy", "answer": "Vorgehensweise", "options": ["grundlegend", "unmittelbar", "Fehlerlos", "Vorgehensweise"]}, {"numb": 15, "question": "lonely", "answer": "Einsam", "options": ["Einsam", "Feindschaft", "Verwendung", "Besch\u00e4ftigung"]}, {"numb": 16, "question": "usage  Kannada: BaLake,", "answer": "Anwendung", "options": ["der Hass", "Sprecher/in", "Anwendung", "Menschheit"]}, {"numb": 17, "question": "compulsory", "answer": "obligatorisch", "options": ["Fahrzeug", "notwending", "Herausforderung", "obligatorisch"]}, {"numb": 18, "question": "need, Avashyakate", "answer": "Bed\u00fcrfnis", "options": ["Bed\u00fcrfnis", "st\u00e4ndig", "Feindschaft", "obligatorisch"]}, {"numb": 19, "question": "imprint, kaalachchu, Mudre", "answer": "Abdruck", "options": ["der Hass", "Verbesserung", "Besch\u00e4ftigung", "Abdruck"]}, {"numb": 20, "question": "active, sakriya, chatuvatikeyindiru", "answer": "aktiv", "options": ["Einsam", "Gegengrund", "Pflicht", "aktiv"]}, {"numb": 21, "question": "constantly, nirantaravagi", "answer": "st\u00e4ndig", "options": ["Ernst", "st\u00e4ndig", "\u00e4hnlich", "Genehmigung"]}, {"numb": 22, "question": "opinion, abhipraya", "answer": "Meinung", "options": ["Meinung", "Kohlenstoffdioxid", "widerspruch", "Vorgang"]}, {"numb": 23, "question": "necessary, required", "answer": "n\u00f6tig", "options": ["grundlegend", "Fortschritt", "aktiv", "n\u00f6tig"]}, {"numb": 24, "question": "Procedure", "answer": "Verfahren", "options": ["Modernizierung", "Verfahren", "Sprecher/in", "befristet"]}, {"numb": 25, "question": "kannada: Sevane, consumption", "answer": "verbrauch", "options": ["Umweltfreundlich", "verbrauch", "Behindert", "einwandfrei"]}, {"numb": 26, "question": "deadly", "answer": "t\u00f6dlich", "options": ["t\u00f6dlich", "Bereich", "Anwendung", "n\u00f6tig"]}, {"numb": 27, "question": "Pressure", "answer": "Druck", "options": ["Druck", "Gewaltlosigkeit", "\ufeffGlobalizierung", "Ernst"]}, {"numb": 28, "question": "Infrastructure", "answer": "Infrastruktur", "options": ["Perspektiv", "t\u00f6dlich", "Infrastruktur", "Verf\u00fcgbar"]}, {"numb": 29, "question": "enmity, Vairatva", "answer": "Feindschaft", "options": ["Stoff", "Ansicht", "Feindschaft", "illegal"]}, {"numb": 30, "question": "marketing", "answer": "Vertrieb", "options": ["Sieg", "Vertrieb", "dauerhaft", "Nutzung"]}, {"numb": 31, "question": "joyful, santoshita", "answer": "Froh", "options": ["Konvertierung", "erforderlich", "Froh", "Gewalt"]}, {"numb": 32, "question": "necessary, required", "answer": "notwending", "options": ["Konvertierung", "erforderlich", "Freude", "notwending"]}, {"numb": 33, "question": "Occupation", "answer": "Besch\u00e4ftigung", "options": ["logik", "Besch\u00e4ftigung", "elementar", "W\u00fcrde"]}, {"numb": 34, "question": "contact person, samparka vyakti", "answer": "Ansprechpartner", "options": ["vorsicht", "Genehmigung", "grunds\u00e4tzlich", "Ansprechpartner"]}, {"numb": 35, "question": "political, raajakiya", "answer": "politisch", "options": ["gewaltsam", "Perspektiv", "politisch", "Vorgang"]}, {"numb": 36, "question": "basic, fundamental", "answer": "elementar", "options": ["Bed\u00fcrfnis", "Verwendung", "Verbesserung", "elementar"]}, {"numb": 37, "question": "combination", "answer": "Kombination", "options": ["Infrastruktur", "Schild, Schilder", "Kombination", "sicht"]}, {"numb": 38, "question": "prerequisites, \u0caa\u0cc2\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0caa\u0cc7\u0c95\u0ccd\u0cb7\u0cbf\u0ca4\u0c97\u0cb3\u0cc1", "answer": "Voraussetzung", "options": ["Abfall", "grundlegend", "Voraussetzung", "widerlich"]}, {"numb": 39, "question": "Nature", "answer": "Klima", "options": ["aktiv", "grunds\u00e4tzlich", "Klima", "Vorgang"]}, {"numb": 40, "question": "No response given", "answer": "Zustand state, condition, sthithi", "options": ["Zustand state, condition, sthithi", "Digitalizierung", "politisch", "Freude"]}, {"numb": 41, "question": "without problems", "answer": "Fehlerlos", "options": ["Betrug", "Grundsatz", "Schild, Schilder", "Fehlerlos"]}, {"numb": 42, "question": "necessary, required", "answer": "erforderlich", "options": ["Ansprechpartner", "besondere", "erforderlich", "sicht"]}, {"numb": 43, "question": "Modernization", "answer": "Modernizierung", "options": ["Hectisch", "Modernizierung", "Verfahren", "Kohlenstoff"]}, {"numb": 44, "question": "loneliness", "answer": "Einsamkeit", "options": ["Kombination", "Abteilung", "Einsamkeit", "Kommunikation"]}, {"numb": 45, "question": "purposefully, uddeshapporvakavagi", "answer": "absichtlich", "options": ["Hindernis", "absichtlich", "ehemalig", "\u00e4hnlich"]}, {"numb": 46, "question": "peace, shaanti", "answer": "Friede", "options": ["dauerhaft", "Kombination", "Lebensw\u00fcrdigkeit", "Friede"]}, {"numb": 47, "question": "overview, pakshinota, avalokana", "answer": "\u00fcbersicht", "options": ["Erfolg", "\u00fcbersicht", "widerwillig", "Perspektiv"]}, {"numb": 48, "question": "immediate, takshanavagi", "answer": "unmittelbar", "options": ["Beglaubigte", "Freundschaft", "Nutzung", "unmittelbar"]}, {"numb": 49, "question": "involvement", "answer": "Beteiligung", "options": ["Beteiligung", "Kohlenstoffdioxid", "Pflicht", "pl\u00f6tzlich"]}, {"numb": 50, "question": "resist, virdoshisu, tadedu nillisu", "answer": "widerstand", "options": ["Fortschritt", "Herausforderung", "widerstand", "Ressource"]}, {"numb": 51, "question": "Policy", "answer": "Grundsatz", "options": ["Qual", "Grundsatz", "widerrechtlich", "Friedlich"]}, {"numb": 52, "question": "Riot, galabhe", "answer": "Randale", "options": ["Randale", "ben\u00f6tigt", "Segen", "Verfahren"]}, {"numb": 53, "question": "impaired, disabled", "answer": "Behindert", "options": ["Behindert", "Freude", "Betrug", "sofort"]}, {"numb": 54, "question": "illegal, kanoonu bahira", "answer": "illegal", "options": ["w\u00fcrdig", "illegal", "erforderlich", "Beteiligung"]}, {"numb": 55, "question": "peaceful, shaantiyuta", "answer": "Friedlich", "options": ["Friedlich", "elementar", "verbrauch", "Fl\u00e4che"]}, {"numb": 56, "question": "Victory, Jaya", "answer": "Sieg", "options": ["widerrechtlich", "sofort", "st\u00e4ndig", "Sieg"]}, {"numb": 57, "question": "Fuel, Indhana", "answer": "Stoff", "options": ["Grundsatz", "befristet", "Stoff", "obligatorisch"]}, {"numb": 58, "question": "pramaanikarisida, dhrudikarisida", "answer": "Beglaubigte", "options": ["Erfolg", "logik", "Beglaubigte", "Voraussetzung"]}, {"numb": 59, "question": "area, Bhoopradesha", "answer": "Fl\u00e4che", "options": ["Natur", "Stoff", "Fl\u00e4che", "notwending"]}, {"numb": 60, "question": "meanwhile, ee naduve, ashtralli", "answer": "inzwischen", "options": ["Abfall", "Einsam", "inzwischen", "Verbesserung"]}, {"numb": 61, "question": "joy, santosha", "answer": "Freude", "options": ["Freude", "obligatorisch", "notwending", "Voraussetzung"]}, {"numb": 62, "question": "corresponding, anuroopavada", "answer": "entsprechende", "options": ["Fehlerlos", "entsprechende", "inzwischen", "Modernizierung"]}, {"numb": 63, "question": "approval", "answer": "Genehmigung", "options": ["aktiv", "Behindert", "W\u00fcrde", "Genehmigung"]}, {"numb": 64, "question": "Nature", "answer": "Natur", "options": ["Umweltfreundlich", "der Hass", "Natur", "Meinung"]}, {"numb": 65, "question": "carbon dioxide", "answer": "Kohlenstoffdioxid", "options": ["Kohlenstoffdioxid", "Fl\u00e4che", "Froh", "Vorgehensweise"]}, {"numb": 66, "question": "violent, himsatmaka", "answer": "brutal", "options": ["obligatorisch", "brutal", "Kombination", "Gebiet"]}, {"numb": 67, "question": "improvment", "answer": "Verbesserung", "options": ["Verfahren", "absichtlich", "Verbesserung", "Treibhauseffekt"]}, {"numb": 68, "question": "abuse, DurbaLake", "answer": "Abnutzung", "options": ["Beglaubigte", "Abnutzung", "Treibhauseffekt", "der Hass"]}, {"numb": 69, "question": "abhivraddhi, progress", "answer": "Fortschritt", "options": ["Grundsatz", "Fortschritt", "Konvertierung", "Perspektiv"]}, {"numb": 70, "question": "Opportunity", "answer": "Gelegenheit", "options": ["Treibhauseffekt", "Gelegenheit", "Vorgehensweise", "ehemalig"]}, {"numb": 71, "question": "suddenly, idakiddante, akaasmat", "answer": "pl\u00f6tzlich", "options": ["pl\u00f6tzlich", "Bereich", "der Hass", "inzwischen"]}, {"numb": 72, "question": "forever, shashwata", "answer": "ewig", "options": ["Kohlenstoffdioxid", "gewaltsam", "ewig", "Anwendung"]}, {"numb": 73, "question": "process, kannada: prakriye", "answer": "Vorgang", "options": ["prinzipiell", "Kohlenstoffdioxid", "Druck", "Vorgang"]}, {"numb": 74, "question": "Carbon monooxide", "answer": "Kohlenstoffmonoxid", "options": ["Verf\u00fcgbar", "Kohlenstoffmonoxid", "Feindschaft", "Ansprechpartner"]}, {"numb": 75, "question": "necessary, required", "answer": "ben\u00f6tigt", "options": ["Friedlich", "Hectisch", "Freundschaft", "ben\u00f6tigt"]}, {"numb": 76, "question": "Cheat, Vanchane, Mosa", "answer": "Betrug", "options": ["Betrug", "Kommunal", "aktiv", "wesentlich"]}, {"numb": 77, "question": "serious, Gambhira", "answer": "Ernst", "options": ["Fortschritt", "prinzipiell", "Ernst", "Anwendung"]}, {"numb": 78, "question": "spokesperson, vaktaar", "answer": "Sprecher/in", "options": ["Herausforderung", "Ansprechpartner", "Sprecher/in", "Kohlenstoffdioxid"]}, {"numb": 79, "question": "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "answer": "prinzipiell", "options": ["prinzipiell", "sicht", "entsprechende", "politisch"]}, {"numb": 80, "question": "Enviornment friendly", "answer": "Umweltfreundlich", "options": ["Umweltfreundlich", "gewaltsam", "sicht", "Perspektiv"]}, {"numb": 81, "question": "Digitalization", "answer": "Digitalizierung", "options": ["\ufeffGlobalizierung", "Digitalizierung", "Lebensw\u00fcrdigkeit", "bestimmt"]}, {"numb": 82, "question": "Blessings, verb is SegNen", "answer": "Segen", "options": ["Ablauf", "Segen", "Qual", "Freude"]}, {"numb": 83, "question": "sign", "answer": "Schild, Schilder", "options": ["Schild, Schilder", "Abfall", "Randale", "Fehlerlos"]}, {"numb": 84, "question": "attentive", "answer": "Aufmerksam", "options": ["gewaltsam", "Absicht", "Kohlenstoff", "Aufmerksam"]}, {"numb": 85, "question": "imemdiately, tatkshana", "answer": "sofort", "options": ["Ressource", "illegal", "sofort", "bestimmt"]}, {"numb": 86, "question": "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "answer": "grunds\u00e4tzlich", "options": ["grunds\u00e4tzlich", "widerspruch", "widerlich", "Bereich"]}, {"numb": 87, "question": "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "answer": "wesentlich", "options": ["widerspruch", "Freude", "wesentlich", "Ernst"]}, {"numb": 88, "question": "special, visheshavada", "answer": "besondere", "options": ["Einsamkeit", "Stoff", "erforderlich", "besondere"]}, {"numb": 89, "question": "process, kannada: prakriye", "answer": "Prozess", "options": ["Prozess", "Nutzung", "Absicht", "obligatorisch"]}, {"numb": 90, "question": "Guideline, Kannada: Maargasoochi", "answer": "Richtlinie", "options": ["Sieg", "Richtlinie", "Aufmerksam", "Pflicht"]}, {"numb": 91, "question": "sarasari", "answer": "durchschnitt", "options": ["durchschnitt", "Fl\u00e4che", "elementar", "Qual"]}, {"numb": 92, "question": "Globalization", "answer": "\ufeffGlobalizierung", "options": ["\ufeffGlobalizierung", "\u00fcbersicht", "Freude", "Lebensw\u00fcrdigkeit"]}, {"numb": 93, "question": "logic, tarka", "answer": "logik", "options": ["logik", "widerlich", "Freundschaft", "Ablauf"]}, {"numb": 94, "question": "communal, komu", "answer": "Kommunal", "options": ["Ansprechpartner", "Kommunal", "inzwischen", "Hindernis"]}, {"numb": 95, "question": "Greenhouse effekt", "answer": "Treibhauseffekt", "options": ["Fachbereich", "Zustand state, condition, sthithi", "Treibhauseffekt", "Freundschaft"]}, {"numb": 96, "question": "Challenge", "answer": "Herausforderung", "options": ["pl\u00f6tzlich", "ehemalig", "\ufeffGlobalizierung", "Herausforderung"]}, {"numb": 97, "question": "Counter argument", "answer": "Gegengrund", "options": ["Betrug", "Klima", "Gegengrund", "Bed\u00fcrfnis"]}, {"numb": 98, "question": "dignity, Ghanathe", "answer": "W\u00fcrde", "options": ["sicht", "einwandfrei", "Ma\u00dfnahme", "W\u00fcrde"]}, {"numb": 99, "question": "ashyakara, disgusting", "answer": "widerlich", "options": ["Friede", "Sprecher/in", "Vorgang", "widerlich"]}, {"numb": 100, "question": "according to..", "answer": "gem\u00e4\u00df+dativ", "options": ["gem\u00e4\u00df+dativ", "Pflicht", "Froh", "Ernst"]}, {"numb": 101, "question": "permanent, shashwata", "answer": "dauerhaft", "options": ["Verbesserung", "Gewalt", "Ansprechpartner", "dauerhaft"]}, {"numb": 102, "question": "Hate, Dwesha", "answer": "der Hass", "options": ["Kombination", "befristet", "der Hass", "Beteiligung"]}, {"numb": 103, "question": "adjective, Perfect, paripoorna", "answer": "einwandfrei", "options": ["einwandfrei", "bestimmt", "\u00fcbersicht", "Kohlenstoff"]}, {"numb": 104, "question": "area, Kshetra", "answer": "Gebiet", "options": ["bestimmt", "Ansprechpartner", "Gebiet", "logik"]}, {"numb": 105, "question": "strategy", "answer": "Strategie", "options": ["betroffene", "Aufmerksam", "Strategie", "durchsichtig"]}, {"numb": 106, "question": "Victory, Jaya", "answer": "Erfolg", "options": ["Erfolg", "Betrug", "grunds\u00e4tzlich", "Sprecher/in"]}, {"numb": 107, "question": "sight, drushti", "answer": "sicht", "options": ["sicht", "Sieg", "Betrug", "entsprechende"]}, {"numb": 108, "question": "similar, holuva, samavada", "answer": "\u00e4hnlich", "options": ["Friede", "\u00e4hnlich", "Freude", "durchsichtig"]}, {"numb": 109, "question": "particular, nirdishtavada", "answer": "bestimmt", "options": ["sofort", "Pflicht", "bestimmt", "widerlich"]}, {"numb": 110, "question": "humanity", "answer": "Menschheit", "options": ["Behindert", "Betrug", "pl\u00f6tzlich", "Menschheit"]}, {"numb": 111, "question": "Carbon", "answer": "Kohlenstoff", "options": ["Kohlenstoff", "Fr\u00f6hlich", "Ansicht", "pl\u00f6tzlich"]}, {"numb": 112, "question": "puprose, uddeesha", "answer": "Absicht", "options": ["wesentlich", "Pflicht", "Absicht", "Druck"]}, {"numb": 113, "question": "caution, precaution, ecchara, jagarookate", "answer": "vorsicht", "options": ["vorsicht", "Genehmigung", "Hectisch", "Abteilung"]}, {"numb": 114, "question": "according to..", "answer": "laut + dativ, laut + gen", "options": ["laut + dativ, laut + gen", "Modernizierung", "Segen", "Fachbereich"]}, {"numb": 115, "question": "opposition,", "answer": "widerspruch", "options": ["widerspruch", "durchsichtig", "Sieg", "Fl\u00e4che"]}, {"numb": 116, "question": "friendship", "answer": "Freundschaft", "options": ["Digitalizierung", "Freundschaft", "Verlauf", "Sieg"]}, {"numb": 117, "question": "KaruNe, Daye", "answer": "Lebensw\u00fcrdigkeit", "options": ["durchschnitt", "Lebensw\u00fcrdigkeit", "Ablauf", "unmittelbar"]}, {"numb": 118, "question": "attention, Gamana", "answer": "Aufmerksamkeit", "options": ["Aufmerksamkeit", "betroffene", "wesentlich", "Abteilung"]}, {"numb": 119, "question": "garbage", "answer": "M\u00fcll", "options": ["M\u00fcll", "entsprechende", "grundlegend", "Verbesserung"]}, {"numb": 120, "question": "communication", "answer": "Kommunikation", "options": ["Meinung", "Natur", "Kommunikation", "gewaltsam"]}, {"numb": 121, "question": "Former, maaji", "answer": "ehemalig", "options": ["ehemalig", "t\u00f6dlich", "W\u00fcrde", "Klima"]}, {"numb": 122, "question": "reluctant, manasillada", "answer": "widerwillig", "options": ["Abteilung", "Nutzung", "Einsam", "widerwillig"]}, {"numb": 123, "question": "Kaavos, Kannda: Gondala", "answer": "Chaos", "options": ["Niederlage", "Chaos", "n\u00f6tig", "Vorgang"]}, {"numb": 124, "question": "transparent, paradarhska", "answer": "durchsichtig", "options": ["gewaltsam", "sofort", "durchsichtig", "Beglaubigte"]}, {"numb": 125, "question": "affected, concerned, baadhitha", "answer": "betroffene", "options": ["Fehlerlos", "Konvertierung", "durchschnitt", "betroffene"]}, {"numb": 126, "question": "process, kannada: prakriye", "answer": "Verlauf", "options": ["Vertrieb", "Freude", "Verlauf", "Gewaltlosigkeit"]}, {"numb": 127, "question": "illegal, kanoonu bahira", "answer": "widerrechtlich", "options": ["widerstand", "widerrechtlich", "Randale", "Verf\u00fcgbar"]}, {"numb": 128, "question": "compulsory", "answer": "Pflicht", "options": ["Aufmerksam", "Pflicht", "logik", "widerstand"]}, {"numb": 129, "question": "against nature, aswabhavika", "answer": "widernat\u00fcrlich", "options": ["Perspektiv", "Verlauf", "widernat\u00fcrlich", "aktiv"]}, {"numb": 130, "question": "Hectic", "answer": "Hectisch", "options": ["t\u00f6dlich", "sofort", "widerstand", "Hectisch"]}, {"numb": 131, "question": "Krama, Measure", "answer": "Ma\u00dfnahme", "options": ["Beglaubigte", "einwandfrei", "Ma\u00dfnahme", "\u00fcbersicht"]}, {"numb": 132, "question": "violent, himsatmaka", "answer": "gewaltsam", "options": ["Gelegenheit", "Behindert", "gewaltsam", "Randale"]}, {"numb": 133, "question": "obstacle, ade tade", "answer": "Hindernis", "options": ["Prozess", "Ma\u00dfnahme", "Absicht", "Hindernis"]}, {"numb": 134, "question": "joyful, nagumogada", "answer": "Fr\u00f6hlich", "options": ["Fr\u00f6hlich", "Freude", "widerstand", "Ma\u00dfnahme"]}, {"numb": 135, "question": "Procedure", "answer": "Ablauf", "options": ["Einsamkeit", "betroffene", "Abteilung", "Ablauf"]}, {"numb": 136, "question": "joyful, santoshadayaka", "answer": "Freudig", "options": ["Freudig", "W\u00fcrde", "Chaos", "n\u00f6tig"]}, {"numb": 137, "question": "dignified", "answer": "w\u00fcrdig", "options": ["w\u00fcrdig", "Richtlinie", "Chaos", "inzwischen"]}, {"numb": 138, "question": "department, ilaakhe", "answer": "Abteilung", "options": ["Herausforderung", "widerrechtlich", "Abteilung", "Strategie"]}, {"numb": 139, "question": "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "answer": "grundlegend", "options": ["grundlegend", "Fortschritt", "Hindernis", "Ansicht"]}, {"numb": 140, "question": "usage  Kannada: BaLake,", "answer": "Verwendung", "options": ["Stoff", "grundlegend", "Verwendung", "Abteilung"]}, {"numb": 141, "question": "prespective, Viewpoint, Drustikona", "answer": "Perspektiv", "options": ["Abfall", "ben\u00f6tigt", "Hindernis", "Perspektiv"]}, {"numb": 142, "question": "operations, business, firm", "answer": "Betrieb", "options": ["Betrieb", "Genehmigung", "Lebensw\u00fcrdigkeit", "inzwischen"]}, {"numb": 143, "question": "Kannda: BaLake", "answer": "Nutzung", "options": ["Nutzung", "Aufmerksam", "t\u00f6dlich", "inzwischen"]}, {"numb": 144, "question": "vehicle, vaahana", "answer": "Fahrzeug", "options": ["Fahrzeug", "notwending", "sofort", "Abfall"]}];